Rodrigo Teixeira Ribeiro da Silva

E-mail rodrigoteix1998@gmail.com

Phone + 55 (19) 99849 - 9946





I began my career as a designer at Raccoon (now Media.Monks Brazil), where I gained knowledge and expertise in the field of UI/UX. At Savvi, I led two squads - graphic design and web development.

Over time, I collaborated on various management processes within the company, particularly those related to process management and recruitment. I became a partner in the company, and under 2 years, we grew from a revenue of 40k to 2MM oh yearly revenue.

Currently, I'm a DevOps Enginner Summer Intern at Eldorado Research Institute.

Professional Experiences

January, 2023 - Now a days

O Hybrid

DevOps Engineer Summer Intern

Instituto de Pesquisas Eldorado - (Research Institute)

Fevereiro de 2021 a Dezembro de 2021

Remote

Web Development Coordinator and Partner Savvi Marketing Digital

- · Management of design and web development squad
- Project management for web development projects
- Development of designs for programmatic media (e.g. Google Ads, Facebook Ads)
- · Development of web prototypes in Figma

Revenue growth from 40k to 2MM (April, 2020 to December, 2021)

April, 2020 - February, 2021

Remote

Design Analyst II Savvi Marketing Digital

October, 2019 - April, 2020

São Carlos - SP

Designer

Raccoon Marketing Digital (Media Monks)

- · Development of designs for social media
- Development of designs for programmatic media (e.g. Google Ads, Facebook Ads)
- Development of design performances reports for stakeholders in English (99 and Didi)

Clients: emDia (Santander), Sim (Santander), 99taxis, Abril Publisher.

August, 2019 a October, 2019

São Carlos - SP

Design Intern

Raccoon Digital Marketing (Media Monks)

Education

2020 - In progress (expected graduation in 2024)

Bachelor's Degree in Information Systems USP (University of São Paulo)

2013 - 2015

Technical Course in Mechanic Engineering Unicamp - Technical College of Limeira (COTIL)

Courses and certifications

Python SQL BI

Introduction to Business Intelligence

Alura

Python SQL BI

ETL Integration Services - Data modelling

Alura

Docker Docker-compose

Docker: managing containers

Alura

Angular 14 Typescript

Angular 14: developing a CRUD

Alura

HTML CSS JS GIT

Discovery - Web Development

Rocketseat

React Typescript Next.js Vite

React.js Specialization

Rocketseat

Node Typescript Nest.js Prisma ORM

Node.js Specialization

Rocketseat In progress

React Typescript Redux Zustand

Redux + Zustand

Rocketseat

EC2 S3 RDS VPC Cloud architecture **Amazon Cloud Pratictioner**

Essintials

Amazon Web Services

Languages

Portuguese Native language.

English

8 years of course in Wizard Idioms School. In 2016 I got a 82 score in the TOEFL exam (not valid anymore)